[
    {
        "id" : 0,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "orange",
            "blue",
            "red"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id" : 1,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "black",
            "white",
            "grey"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id" : 2,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "orange",
            "white",
            "blue"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id" : 3,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "black",
            "pink",
            "orange"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id" : 4,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "blue",
            "orange",
            "pink"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id" : 5,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "black",
            "white",
            "purple"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id" : 5,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "purple",
            "white",
            "pink"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id" : 6,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "purple",
            "white",
            "pink"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id" : 7,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "red",
            "black",
            "yellow"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 0
    },
    {
        "id" : 8,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "purple",
            "white",
            "yellow"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id" : 9,
        "question": "What is this colour?",
        "answers": [
            "blue",
            "green",
            "red"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
    }
]